Sanjay Kumar Mohapatra E-Mail:sanjay9438194280@gmail.com

At: Narasinghpur,Ranpur,NAYAGARH,752026

Mob: - 9438194280, 8249071629

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am sincere, and give all my efforts for the development of organization/company. A position in which will utilize my practical and theoretical experience, knowledge and skill and provide an opportunity for professional and personal growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- 1 : Work as a Sam(sales manager) at Birla Sun Life Insurance from August 2013 to Nov 2014 at Anugul Branch.
- 2: Work as a LIC (BM CLUB) Agent from 2016 to February 2022.
- 3 : Work as a SRM at Bharati Axa Life Insurance from February 2022 to till date 03/01/23

ACADEMIC CREDENTIALS

- Bachelor of Arts from Ranpur College (1997).
- Intermediate in Arts from C H S E, Orissa (1994).
- High School from B.S.E., Orissa (1992).

STRENGTH

- Honesty, self-confidence, punctual and willingness to learn.
- Good communication skill, quick learn and adaptive to new environment.
- Determination strong will power, hard work, promptness & sharpness in performing Duties & capability to persuade and other.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Reading Newspaper.
- Surfing Internet.

PERSONAL PROFILE

Father : Satyabadi Mohapatra

Date of Birth : 01st May 1977

Nationality : Indian Marital Status : Married

Languages Known : English, Hindi, and Oriya.

DECLARATION

All the statement made above is true and genuine, complete & correct. I hereby declare that it contains no information that are false.

Place: BHUBANESWAR

Date:

Sanjay Kumar Mohapatra